Kevin Cheruiyot

36067 Ngara Nairobi +25410015474 kelcheone@gmail.com

A Software engineer with experience in designing, debugging and implementing, and deploying code. Developed products using primarily JavaScript, Html/CSS, Rust, Solidity, Python, PSQL, GraphQ L, and AssemblyScript. But excited to grow and learn new languages, frameworks, and database systems from Deep Learning, ML, Internet of things to Blockchain technologies (Smart Contracts, Governance, and NFTs) and General networking.

EXPERIENCE

Gitcoin, Remote— Opensource Contributor

August 2020 - PRESENT

Worked on various projects as a bug bounty hunter and hackathon participant with protocols like the badger Dao, gitcoin Dao, perp, etc.

Upwork, Remote-Freelancer

January 2021- PRESENT

I have been working on several projects on the Upwork platform as a web developer freelancer.

EDUCATION

KCA University, Nairobi Kenya— Degree

August 2019 - December 2023

Pursuing a Bachelors's degree in Software Development.

Dapp University, Remote-learning— *Certificate*

April 2020 - June 2021

Completed the Blockchain Bootcamp covering all web3 stuff

PROJECTS

Kylaswap – DEX

Kylaswapp is a decentralized exchange built on the ropsten testnet network which leverages an order book to do all the assets exchange between the users. It is built with solidity and deployed

SKILLS

- 1. Web development
- 2. Javascript, HTML, CSS
- 3. React.
- 4. Nodejs.
- 5. Graphql, The Graph
- 6. Chainlink
- 7. Solidity.
- 8. Web3js & Ethers
- 9. Hardhat and Truffle
- 10. Assembly.
- 11. Python.
- 12. IPFS.

AWARDS

Kudos NFT awards won several kudos NFTS from the gitcoin kudos completion rewards.

LANGUAGES

English, Swahili

SOCIALS

Github:

https://github.com/kelcheone